Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Marc Brown Papers
1996 -- 2004
1994 -- 2007
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Brown, Marc
MS148
115.81 Linear Feet 24 record cartons, 16 oversize boxes, 1 half letter sized box, 682 VHS videocassettes
685 Audiovisual Object(s)
1 Digital Object(s) Disk image available for reading room access.
This collection contains material related to the animated children's television shows Arthur and Postcards from Buster, both produced by WGBH-Boston. The collection contains both print and audiovisual material, including scripts, character/props model packages, storyboards, VHS tapes, audiocassettes, CDs, and DVDs.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Marc Brown, 2008 and 2011, accessions 2008.068 and 2011.067, and WGBH, 2020, accession MS-2020-046.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: Arthur print material; Arthur audiovisual material; Postcards from Buster print material; and Postcards from Buster audiovisual material.
Biographical / Historical
Marc Brown (1946-) is an American author and illustrator best known for creating the children's character Arthur the aardvark, the lovable third-grader from Elwood City. Born November 25, 1946, in Erie, Pennsylvania, Brown spent most of his early childhood surrounded by pen, pencils, and paper. His grandmother Thora had an enormous influence on Brown at an early age, and he used her encouragement when he decided to pursue painting at the Cleveland Institute of Art. After exploring all types of mediums, Brown knew that he wanted to pursue a career in illustration, specifically concentrating on the illustration of children's books.
Although this was the path that Brown wanted to take, he was not always encouraged by his peers at the Institute. In fact, Brown has been quoted as saying, "When I let my interest in children's book illustration be known, I got the definite message that the field was absolutely the lowest rung on the artistic ladder." Shortly after graduating in 1969 with a B.F.A. in painting, Brown presented sample drawings to the Boston, Massachusetts publisher Houghton-Mifflin who told him that they would contact him in the event that they were interested. Luckily, they did. With this first experience in illustrating for a major publisher, Brown learned more about the professional world of illustrating and decided to make it his career.
After a short time spent illustrating textbooks, Brown decided to expand into more creative outlets and did so with his first non-textbook illustration, Issac Asimov's What Makes the Sun Shine? After steadily working as an illustrator for other authors for several years, Brown's most famous character evolved after telling his son a bedtime story one night. The story was about an aardvark named Arthur with a very large nose. This bedtime story eventually became a children's book appropriately titled Arthur's Nose, which was published in 1976.
After the success of Arthur's Nose, Brown began to publish even more books about the endearing aardvark. However, not until the debut of the animated television show Arthur, on the Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) network, did the popularity of the Arthur books (as well as the television series) really skyrocket. Since the success of the show, the Arthur program has won the prestigious George Foster Peabody Award and three daytime Emmy Awards for Outstanding Children's Animated Program. It has also won the accolades of parents and teachers alike for its emphasis on literacy as well as various children's issues.
The success of the Arthur series has garnered interest in another character from the same series-Buster Baxter, the cheerful and outgoing rabbit who is also Arthur's best friend. Buster now has his own series, Postcards from Buster, which focuses on his travels to various places, primarily in the United States, with his father. The show gained notoriety in 2005 when it attracted the attention of U.S. Department of Education Secretary, Margaret E. Spellings, for including a lesbian couple on the show. Spellings wrote to PBS, "Many parents would not want their young children exposed to the lifestyles portrayed in the episode." As a result of the controversy, PBS pulled the episode and did not distribute it to its affiliate stations. On a more positive note, Buster has received a Parent's Choice Television Award and has also been nominated for two Emmy Awards. It continues to gain popularity with children and parents alike, and has been praised for its emphasis on exposing kids to different cultures as well as its focus on developing language skills.
Brown looks for inspiration in everyday situations for his beloved characters and other projects. "I feel like a professional eavesdropper," he admitted to John Micklos, Jr. in Reading Today. "I'm always listening for situations that are important for kids and families." Arthur continues to be the most watched show on PBS and one of the highest rated children's shows in North American television history. Brown remains the executive producer of the show and is involved in new and exciting projects, both within the Arthur world and in other creative outlets.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material related to the animated children's television shows Arthur and Postcards from Buster, both produced by WGBH-Boston. The collection contains both print and audiovisual material. The bulk of the material is from 1996 to 2004. The print material for both shows contains scripts, character/props model packages, storyboards, and other material integral to the production process. Of note is material with original comments from Marc Brown as well as sketches of characters and locations.
With more than 600 items, the audiovisual material consists of VHS tapes, audiocassettes, CDs, and DVDs of both Cinar Animation and Cookie Jar Entertainment created files and WGBH episodes. Of note are VHS tapes of the various stages of the editing process (for both Arthur and Postcards from Buster) as well as audiocassettes of actors' auditions for Arthur. There are also several items related to the show's musical numbers, commercial bumpers, and promotional items.
Production files, or files created by Cinar Animation and Cookie Jar Entertainment, mean that the order of the files i.e. by production number, are not the original order in which WGBH aired them. Therefore, files that are grouped together by their respective production numbers are in the order in which they were produced, not aired. This was the original order of the material. Episodes refer to the order in which WGBH aired them and the animation that most people see during an Arthur episode. Titles for production files were taken from official WBGH Arthur and Postcards from Buster production and episode lists. All titles are the final titles used for the show at the time of airing. There are several production files with working titles. These are either noted on the folder or the actual item itself. Titles according to the type of record i.e. location designs/backgrounds, are consistent throughout the series despite variations among these titles throughout the production stages. All Arthur material-both print and audiovisual-is divided into two separate segments. This is noted by A and B in the production files. WGBH episodes also have two segments. This is noted by both the episode number and title of the episode.
Marc Brown; Arthur (Television program); Postcards from Buster (Television program); Media and broadcast history
- Arthur print material, 1994 -- 2007; 1994 -- 2000; MS148.001; 49 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) Disk image available for reading room access.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Cinar Animation and Cookie Jar Entertainment created scripts; character, incidental and props model packages; backgrounds, location designs, storyboards, and other material related to the show's production. Files range from 1 to 124A. The bulk of the material is from 1994 to 2000. Original comments by Marc Brown appear in many of the files. Of note are comments on revisions and needed changes during the various stages of the production process. Other production files include Arthur's Perfect Christmas, Kideo Video: Arthur's New Friend, and Arthur: It's Only Rock 'n' Roll, starring the Backstreet Boys.
  This series also contains the Arthur Style Guide, which was designed to familiarize Arthur production staff with the themes, characters, and branding of various Arthur productions.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by production number, with the exception of the Arthur Style Guide, which is arranged at the end of the series.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Opening credits, backgrounds, color; incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Notes on main character designs, location designs and color background, 1994 -- 1995; MS148.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, storyboard, page 12 edit, 1995; MS148.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, ink sketch of D.W. with flashlight, scene 17, 1994; MS148.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, script, third draft, 1994; MS148.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes; 1B: D.W. imaginary friend; 2A: Francine's bad hair day; 2B: Arthur's family vacation, comments on music, 1995; MS148.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes; 1B: D.W. imaginary friend, music, notes on cues and transitions, 1995; MS148.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes; 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, Greg's music notes, 1995; MS148.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Arthur's eyes, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, Nadine, notes on character, 1995; MS148.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, script, fourth draft, 1994; MS148.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - 1B: D.W.'s imaginary friend, background, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - 2A: Francine's bad hair day, script, third draft, 1994; MS148.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - 2A: Francine's bad hair day, story board, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - 2A: Francine's bad hair day, pencil sketch of Francine in wig, notes on character and location designs, 1995; MS148.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - 2A: Francine's bad hair day, oversized location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - 2B: Arthur's family vacation, incidental character model package and model sheet, 1995; MS148.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - 2B: Arthur's family vacation, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - 2B: Arthur's family vacation, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - 2B: Arthur's family vacation, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - 2B: Arthur's family vacation, oversized location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business, script, first draft, 1994; MS148.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business; 3B: The real Mr. Ratburn, video rough cut notes, 1995; MS148.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business; 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, comments on music, 1995; MS148.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - 3A: Arthur's pet business, background, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, inciddental character model package and model sheet, 1995; MS148.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, inciddental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, location designs/backgrounds, part 1 of 2, 1995; MS148.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, location designs/backgrounds, part 2 of 2, 1995; MS148.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - 3B: Arthur and the real Mr. Ratburn, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp, script, final, 1995; MS148.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp, Arthur in bathing suit, 1995; MS148.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - 4A: Arthur goes to camp; 5B: Arthur's chicken pox, notes on sound, music and animation, 1995; MS148.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - 4B: D.W. thinks big, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - 4B: D.W. thinks big, script, final, 1995; MS148.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - 4B: D.W. thinks big, notes on music and animation, 1995; MS148.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - 4B: D.W. thinks big, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - 4B: D.W. thinks big, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - 5A: Arthur's new puppy, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - 5A: Arthur's new puppy, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - 5A: Arthur's new puppy, notes on music and animation, 1995; MS148.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - 5B: Arthur's chicken pox, script, second draft, 1995; MS148.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - 5B: Arthur's chicken pox, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - 5B: Arthur's chicken pox, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, main character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, rough cut notes, 1995; MS148.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - 6A: Arthur, world's greatest gleeper, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, main character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, incidental character model package, page 4, 1995; MS148.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, rough cut notes, 1995; MS148.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - 6B: Arthur's spelling trubble, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - 7A: Arthur babysits, script, second draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - 7A: Arthur babysits, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - 7A: Arthur babysits, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - 7A: Arthur babysits, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - 7B: D.W. all wet, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - 7B: D.W. all wet, script, thrid draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - 7B: D.W. all wet, notes on sound and animation, 1995; MS148.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - 7B: D.W. all wet, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, script, second draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, ink sketch of general store, 1995; MS148.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, notes on sound and animation, 1995; MS148.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - 8A: Grandpa Dave's old country farm, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - 8B: Arthur writes a story, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - 8B: Arthur writes a story, storyboard, recording, 1995; MS148.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - 9A: Arthur's lost dog, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, script, third draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, incidental character model package, ink sketch of Bitzi Baxter, 1996; MS148.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, storyboard, sheet direction, 1995; MS148.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - 9B: Arthur accused!, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!; 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, notes on sound and animation, 1995; MS148.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, notes on outline, 1995; MS148.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, script, outline, 1995; MS148.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, ink sketch of library, 1995; MS148.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - 10A: Locked in the library!, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, notes on logo sketches, 1995; MS148.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, storyboard, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, incidental character model package with model sheet, 1995; MS148.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - 10B: The scare-your-pants-off club, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - 11A: Arthur's birthday, script, outline, 1995; MS148.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - 11A: Arthur's birthday, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - 11A: Arthur's birthday, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - 11A: Arthur's birthday, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - 11A: Arthur's birthday, locations package; incidental character package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, outline, 1995; MS148.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - 11B: Arthur and the crunch cereal contest, locations package, item 26, 1995; MS148.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, ink sketch of Mrs. Tibble's house and backyard, 1995; MS148.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - 12A: Arthur bounces back, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, location designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - 12B: Bully for Binky, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, script, outline, 1995; MS148.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, script, second draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.002.00072 (Box 2)
  - 13A: Arthur's tooth, location, designs/backgrounds, 1995; MS148.001.002.00073 (Box 2)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, script, outline, 1995; MS148.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, script, final draft, 1995; MS148.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, incidental character model package, rough, 1995; MS148.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, storyboard, dyaxis, 1995; MS148.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - 13B: Arthur and the true Francine, incidental character model pacakge, rough, 1995; MS148.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, script, outline, 1995; MS148.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, script, first draft, 1995; MS148.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, incidental character model package, 1995; MS148.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, backgrounds, color, 1995; MS148.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - 14A: D.W. rides again, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1995; MS148.001.003.00012 (Box 3)